Uhuh
ừ ừ
[music]
[âm nhạc]
when buying Mid-Autumn Festival Super D, the earthly realm with little
khi mua trung thu Super D chân gian cùng
children celebrating the festival, watching the moon fly, the earthly realm, the
em thơ đón tết trông trăng bay em trần
burial place, together here, so that the
gian nơi chôn cất cùng trong đây để sao
two are not cold, together with the community,
hai cũng không lạnh cùng với công cộng
farmers need to listen to the stars singing, together with the
đồng nông cần nghe sao hát cùng dòng
famous line, throwing blows, when brother, let's come
danh lòng tung đòn khi anh ơi hãy cùng
down here, see Anh Tho singing, asking to borrow
xuống đây thấy Anh Thơ hát ca đòi mượn
myself, there is Uncle Cuoi sitting, we are
mình thu có chú cuội ngồi chúng tôi tục
more vulgar, even though it is uncomfortable, that inside, that is
hơn dù khó chịu rằng bên trong rằng là
la la o,
la la ó
you must be the most obedient, the two students
em hết phải chăm ngoan nhất hai học trò
must study well, help mother with housework, that's right,
phải học giỏi này giúp mẹ việc nhà đúng
at home, Sister Hang and Uncle Cuoi have a
rồi ở được nhà chị Hằng Chú Cuội có một
small gift, wanting to catch the little children, so during the
món quà nhỏ muốn bắt các bạn nhỏ nên mùa
Mid-Autumn Festival, work is busy, Sister Hang and Uncle
trung thu công việc lu bu Chị Hằng Chú
Cuoi still want to convey their full feelings
Cuội vẫn muốn gửi gắm tình cảm đong đầy
through this song, wishing you all a
qua bài hát này chúc các em cũng một mùa
happy Mid-Autumn Festival, Mid-Autumn Festival, wishing life, the
trung thu vui vẻ mùa trung thu chúc cuộc
earthly realm with little children celebrating the festival, watching the
đời Trần Gian cùng em thơ đón tết trông
moon fly, my dear, the earthly realm is filled with stars, together
trăng bay Em ơi trần gian thấm đều sao
with the command, needing meaning, singing together with
cùng dòng lệnh cần nghĩa sao hát cùng
Lam Tung's voice, President, the heart, the
giọng Lâm Tùng công Tổng thống tâm Các
Stars singing together with a cold voice, throwing blows
Vì Sao hát cùng giọng lạnh lùng tung
in the community,
trong cộng đồng ý
E HK sitting, wishing sisters, also have names in
Ê HK ngồi chúc chị em cũng có tên trong
the hundred, la la la
trăm là la la la
A and  Be good, study hard, you must study well,
A và chăm ngoan học giỏi phải học giỏi
help Mom with the
này đựng cơm canh cũng giúp mẹ đẹp nhà
housework, and Sister Hang will stand by the
làm việc nhà chị Hằng nó sẽ đứng bánh
mooncakes, and Uncle Cuoi will give you many
trung thu còn chú cuội sẽ cho em nhiều
gifts this Mid-Autumn Festival. I have wholeheartedly taken care
quà mùa trung thu này đã hết lòng chăm
of Uncle Cuoi and Sister Hang this Mid-Autumn Festival. I
cùng chú Cuội chị Hằng mùa trung thu em
came under the moon with Uncle Cuoi and Sister Hang,
đã đến trong trăng cùng chú Cuội chị
through the Mid-Autumn Festival with me, I came under the moon
Hằng qua trung cùng em đến trong trăng
with Uncle Cuoi, yes, yes,
cùng chú Cuội chị ạ ạ
when we little children are always good, study
khi chúng các em nhỏ luôn chăm ngoan học
hard, and love everyone.
giỏi yêu thương mọi người ạ